Welcome back to today's new T12 topic. So today's MongoDB T12 series. So today we're going to
explore for how to create the collections in MongoDB and the collections in the MongoDB are
analogies for table in relation database and more container. And first of all,
simply I can just create a collection of the MongoDB. It's just straightforward and can be done
using the database collection method in the MongoDB shell. And you can choose for the shell
and now I can just select for the comparison here. I can perfectly basically create the
collection. So you can try for the MongoDB shell and perfectly create for the collection for
in your database collection. So now just go for again the main for the MongoDB database and
connection for the new collection and here I can first of all create the new table. So I can just
go here the new table. So here I can use for suppose simply just type for the DB for the database
name and now here I can just choose for here is a simply just drag the bottom line.
You do okay this is a collection name and here I can simply just click the square button
and perfectly you already know use for here the my new TV. Okay so now I can just create
and here simply just I can just use and you can use the old lady. So now I can just
create and perfectly use the database. Okay so define these now database and now simply here I
can just type for the base. Okay and just create and you can see here perfectly created for the new
database or the collection. Okay so now select the data now I can go there are type and here first
one simply create for the first here the data and also create for the collection name for the base. Okay.
So here I can create for another new collection just create. So here I can use for the collection name
for suppose like the information or the documents. So now just type the documents. So the
documents just perfectly create and just here I can create for the collection button and you
can see here add for more collection and now you can choose for here another collection just
create. So now just click for another collection. So now use the collection for like the information
okay. So now here use for another collection name and just create. So here I can press for this
collection button and this series for you can see here you can choose for the time series
and it's the sequence major main over the pure okay. So now I can use this step and now simply
create for the collection name and just create for the collection button okay. So you can see here
perfectly the style created this and now type for the export data update data and did a data.
So you can choose for the let document. So now just go for the next tutorial provide and now
here the session I can create for the three new collection. So first of all create the base collection
then the document then also for the information okay. So I can just remove all this collection.
So you can just press for this and just select for the based and now here simply for the post
for the new remove this collection. So just run this the base okay. So now the all the capital
world for the process for the name given. Now here just simply just remove all for the document table
sorry just the database. So simply here I can just remove for in this database for just press
here the did it and now just redep here the database create for the MongoDB and just drop for
simply in this database okay. You can see here perfectly drop for this collection database we
also the context okay. So I hope you perfectly understand and use the MongoDB common comparison.
I have tried my best to perfectly explain for creating the collection in the MongoDB.
I hope you find this tutorial helpful. So stay tuned for more MongoDB tips and tricks okay.
So thank you for watching and happy data coding, okay?